#### Contact

netali514@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/netaliagrawal (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Business Intelligence (BI)
Data Visualization
Data Analysis

### Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi

Certifications
LOMA 280

# Netali Agrawal

Data Scientist at Infosys

Hyderabad

## Summary

Experienced Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Data Analytics, machine learning, business intelligence, data visualization, SQL and SDLC. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) focused in Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering from Global Institute of Technology.

## Experience

Infosys

6 years 9 months

**Data Scientist** 

March 2020 - Present (6 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana

Working as Data Scientist for Supply Chain Analytics Domain

Technology Lead

April 2016 - March 2020 (4 years)

Hyderabad Area, India

Technology Analyst

December 2013 - March 2016 (2 years 4 months)

Co-learning lounge

Community Builder (Core team and Mentor)

June 2020 - Present (3 months)

The Co-learning lounge is the fastest-growing tech community in a mission to open-source education hence making it affordable. Unlike other communities, they are solving the core problems through community collaboration. That is Learning, Mentoring, Job referral, and Connecting with like-minded people. They conduct offline and online events to bring the best of the experienced industry people to talk about Data Science to anything that helps you to grow professionally.

Subscribe to their YouTube channel to never miss any live session in the future and join their AI telegram community to stay connected with like-minded folks.

YouTube channel: https://bit.ly/CLLYT
Telegram channel: https://bit.ly/CLL\_TG
Visit https://colearninglounge.com for more

Capgemini India Pvt. Ltd.

Associate Consultant

April 2013 - November 2013 (8 months)

Working with the team to deliver the best solution to the client and the expected time.

Capgemini

2 years 8 months

Senior System Engineer April 2012 - March 2013 (1 year)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

System Engineer

August 2010 - March 2012 (1 year 8 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Max Bupa

CCE

January 2010 - August 2010 (8 months)

Handling the customers with their queries in the best possible way.

## Education

Great Lakes Institute of Management

Post Graduate program in BABI, Data Science · (2018 - 2019)

Global Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2005 - 2009)

St. Mary's Convent Inter College

Maths · (1993 - 2005)